

- abadahela@gmail.com
- https://helabedaporfolio.vercel.app
- material Tunisian
- +216 21 593 065

Social networks

in @hela-abada-b0b560120/

@helabeda

Languages

Arabic

French

English

Certificats

Fullstack Js MERN developer GOMYCODE

LinkedIn Learning

Février 2021

• Python: L'analyse de données

LinkedIn Learning

Mars 2021

• L'essentiel du HTML5

LinkedIn Learning

Février 2021

 Les fondements de la programmation

Compétences

Figma

Tailwind

Express.js

Redux

Material-Ul

Bootstrap

HTML 5

CSS3

JavaScript / ES6

React.Js

Trello

API / RestAPI

Node.js

MongoDB/ Mongoose

Git, GitHub, GitLab

FullStack JS Web Developer

"Holding a degree in Electrical Engineering, specializing in Embedded Electronics and Telecommunications, I am versatile and autonomous in my role while enjoying working in a team. With 2 years of experience, I have specialized in Full Stack JS development and website creation, although I am also capable of website deployment and web design. I am currently seeking new opportunities."

Education and Training

Full-Stack Javascript Bootcamp Certificate

From May 2021 to October 2021 GO MY CODE Gafsa, Tunisie

Java Certificate

From January 2021 to March 2021 Electroworks Gafsa, Tunisie

National Engineering Diploma

From September 2015 to July 2018

ESPRIMS - Private Superior School of Engineers Monastir, Tunisie

• Specialization: Embedded Electronics and Telecommunications

Bachelor's Degree in Electrical Engineering

From September 2012 to June 2015

Higher Institute of Technological Studies Gafsa, Tunisie

Specialization: Industrial Electricity.

Expériences professionnelles

FullStack developer

From July 2022 to December 2022 Highway Tunis, Tunisie

- Creating MERN stack applications.
- Backend (NodeJS) and frontend (ReactJS) development of the website for the startup International Highway.
- Maintenance, improvement, addition of new modules to the site, and bug fixes.
- Development of the site and its responsive version.
- Working with Figma for designing web and mobile applications.
- Orchestration of application deployment with continuous deployment tools.

FullStack Web Developer

Since November 2021 Freelance

- · Creation of MERN stack applications.
- Creation of RESTful services with Node.js.
- Programmation des codes responsives.
- Creation of e-commerce sites.

Electrical Engineer

From August 2020 to December 2020

Electrical Works for Industrial Building TEBI Tunis, Tunisie

Adjunct Professor

From September 2019 to July 2020

Higher Institute of Technological Studies ISET Gafsa, Tunisie

- Sensor Course.
- Measurement and Metrology Course.
- Computer-Aided Design (CAD) Practical Work (using ISIS, ARES, and designing electronic cards).

Assets

Time Management Skills

Leadership Skills

Adaptability and Flexibility

Technical Expertise

Excellent Communication Skills

Strong Problem-Solving Skills